QUESTIONS = [
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: The thieves invaded his house while he was in the United Kingdom and swept it clean of every valuable property. (Which of the following strategies can a reader adopt to arrive at the meaning of the passage?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Co-text",
      "B": "Past experiences",
      "C": "Lexical familiarisation",
      "D": "Word attack"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Indicate whether skimming or scanning: Locating the names of the main characters in a passage",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "scanning "
  },
  {
    "question": "Looking at the merits and demerits of what is heard will involve ________",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "critical analysis"
  },
  {
    "question": " Listening is said to be useless if there is no _______",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "comprehension"
  },
  {
    "question": "The length of a note written during a seminar will affect one of the following aspects of its content.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Logicality",
      "B": "Revised content",
      "C": "Brevity",
      "D": "Topicality"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "The following words: \u2018next\u2019, \u2018finally\u2019 signal _____ in a speech.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Valid points",
      "B": "Debatable points",
      "C": "Important points",
      "D": "Exaggerated points"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gap: 'Everyone truly needs to be careful in these days of increasing _1___ crimes. I got a mail the other day, asking me to __2__ my banking app. The sender promised I would be able to have access to my 3___interests once the process was completed. On a second thought, I decided to speak with my sister who is a banker first. She told me if I had carried out the action, I would have made the criminal a _4___ who would have access to all my lifetime ___5__ (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 4.)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Beneficiary",
      "B": "Relation",
      "C": "Signatory",
      "D": "Manager"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Skimming is a term which refers to the ___ reading speed.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Slowest",
      "B": "Slow",
      "C": "Average",
      "D": "Fastest"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "The following expression: \u2018Do not remove your seat belt\u2019 is an example of information given in form of a__-.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Direction",
      "B": "Facts",
      "C": "Evaluation",
      "D": "Instruction"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: As a Nigerian, Olubiyi is __1__ with regards to language use. His father had many wives and the polygamous nature of his family exposed him to diverse cultures. His friends accuse him of being ___2__ because he can hardly keep secret. His wife however believes he is not as unserious as everyone thinks but that he could actually be _3__ when assessing situations. (Which of the following is the best option for number 2?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Restive",
      "B": "Garrulous",
      "C": "Sarcastic",
      "D": "taciturn"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: As a Nigerian, Olubiyi is __1__ with regards to language use. His father had many wives and the polygamous nature of his family exposed him to diverse cultures. His friends accuse him of being ___2__ because he can hardly keep secret. His wife however believes he is not as unserious as everyone thinks but that he could actually be _3__ when assessing situations. (Which of the following is the best option for number 1?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Multilingual",
      "B": "Bi-part lingual",
      "C": "Homolingual",
      "D": "Monolingual"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of these terms refers to the most exciting point in a story",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Climax",
      "B": "Exposition",
      "C": "Plot",
      "D": "Argument"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gap: Everyone truly needs to be careful in these days of increasing _1___ crimes. I got a mail the other day, asking me to __2__ my banking app. The sender promised I would be able to have access to my 3___interests once the process was completed. On a second thought, I decided to speak with my sister who is a banker first. She told me if I had carried out the action, I would have made the criminal a _4___ who would have access to all my lifetime ___5__ (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 1)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Cyber",
      "B": "Technology",
      "C": "Global",
      "D": "Data"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Skimming could aid a reader\u2019s ___ impression of a report.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Critical",
      "B": "General",
      "C": "Collaborative",
      "D": "Evaluative"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: Okonkwo and Ige are childhood friends. The duo also attended the University of Lagos. Someone has described them as twins from different mothers and I agree.     (Which reading strategy did the writer use to make the meaning of words clearer in the passage?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Lexical familiarisation",
      "B": "Co-text",
      "C": "Past experiences",
      "D": "Word attack"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the following strategies could enhance a language learner\u2019s vocabulary.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Evaluative reading",
      "B": "Fastest reading",
      "C": "Extensive reading",
      "D": "Study reading"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following parts of the sentence: \u2018The major challenge that Nigeria is currently facing is food shortage\u2019 is used by the speaker to signal a main idea?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Nigeria is currently",
      "B": "Is",
      "C": "food shortage",
      "D": "The major challenge"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "All but ONE of the following reading activities require slow reading speed.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Studying a topic in geophysics",
      "B": "Reading for an examination",
      "C": "Locating an address from yellow pages",
      "D": "Reading an engineering textbook"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reading at the fastest speed is needed when you want to _______",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "locate information quickly"
  },
  {
    "question": "One important way of increasing your vocabulary is to _______",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "read intensively and extensively"
  },
  {
    "question": "The_______ needs high concentration and particular attention to specific details.",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "study reading speed"
  },
  {
    "question": "A reader who uses average speed will likely achieve __ level of comprehension if s/he reads 250-500 words per minute.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": 0.7,
      "B": 0.5,
      "C": 1,
      "D": 0.3
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following reading speed is appropriate for a student who wants to read Buchi Emechenta\u2019s novel titled: The Joys of Motherhood?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Average",
      "B": "Slow",
      "C": "Fastest",
      "D": "Slowest"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "The term blurb refers to the ____ of a book.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Content",
      "B": "Summary",
      "C": "Critique",
      "D": "Introduction"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following resources could make a text vivid?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Symbols",
      "B": "Charts",
      "C": "Abbreviation",
      "D": "Transitional words"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uche\u2019s picture taken at the wedding is ICONIC",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Legendary",
      "B": "Attractive",
      "C": "Big",
      "D": "Scandalous"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gaps: Uche went for her regular check-up recently and discovered to her amazement that her __1_ mass indicated that she was ginning weight. She was also found to have a _2__ level. She decided it was best she registered with a GYM close to her house for ___3_ classes. She also needed to have a change of __4____ because she was becoming __5___ to sweet drinks. It was not going to be easy but she made up her mind to give it all it takes to be healthy. (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 4.)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Outlook",
      "B": "Worldview",
      "C": "Lifestyle",
      "D": "Perspective"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the following devise is used by a writer to retain the attention of a reader.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Facts",
      "B": "Climax",
      "C": "Suspense",
      "D": "Plot"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gaps: Uche went for her regular check-up recently and discovered to her amazement that her __1_ mass indicated that she was ginning weight. She was also found to have a _2__ level. She decided it was best she registered with a GYM close to her house for ___3_ classes. She also needed to have a change of __4____ because she was becoming __5___ to sweet drinks. It was not going to be easy but she made up her mind to give it all it takes to be healthy. (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 2.)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Cholesterol",
      "B": "Phobia",
      "C": "Interest",
      "D": "Infection"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage:  Many years ago, Dotun married his wife Morenike. Morenike was a humble lady. She was a supportive wife too. However, for more than six years, they were childless. Anytime Morenike felt sad, her family and friends would cheer her up because she was such a good soul. In 1990, which was almost seven years later, they were blessed with two a beautiful set of twins  (Which of the options is the term for this type of text?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Argumentative",
      "B": "Expository",
      "C": "Narrative",
      "D": "Descriptive"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gaps: Uche went for her regular check-up recently and discovered to her amazement that her __1_ mass indicated that she was ginning weight. She was also found to have a _2__ level. She decided it was best she registered with a GYM close to her house for ___3_ classes. She also needed to have a change of __4____ because she was becoming __5___ to sweet drinks. It was not going to be easy but she made up her mind to give it all it takes to be healthy. (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 1.)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Muscular",
      "B": "Body",
      "C": "Mental",
      "D": "Data"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage: Good day, everyone. Today, I am going to show you how to paint a room in your home. First, you need to choose a paint colour. You also need to choose a finish which will  affect how glossy and durable the paint will be once it is dry. Make sure you also get the right paint brush, so that the process is made easy. When you are ready, start by making a straight line on the wall with your brush. Please note that you are to dip the brush halfway into the paint and tap off any excess before applying each time on the wall (The information provided in the passage is in form of _____)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Instruction",
      "B": "Fables",
      "C": "Myth",
      "D": "Description"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gaps: Uche went for her regular check-up recently and discovered to her amazement that her __1_ mass indicated that she was ginning weight. She was also found to have a _2__ level. She decided it was best she registered with a GYM close to her house for ___3_ classes. She also needed to have a change of __4____ because she was becoming __5___ to sweet drinks. It was not going to be easy but she made up her mind to give it all it takes to be healthy. (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 5.)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Accustomed",
      "B": "Addicted",
      "C": "Adopted",
      "D": "Adapted"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the following forms of writing is sometimes the product of imagination.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Scientific texts",
      "B": "Narrative texts",
      "C": "Argumentative texts",
      "D": "Expository texts"
    },
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage: Good day, everyone. Today, I am going to show you how to paint a room in your home. First, you need to choose a paint colour. You also need to choose a finish which will  affect how glossy and durable the paint will be once it is dry. Make sure you also get the right paint brush, so that the process is made easy. When you are ready, start by making a straight line on the wall with your brush. Please note that you are to dip the brush halfway into the paint and tap off any excess before applying each time on the wall (Which of the options is the term for this type of text?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Argumentative",
      "B": "Expository",
      "C": "Narrative",
      "D": "Descriptive"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gaps: Uche went for her regular check-up recently and discovered to her amazement that her __1_ mass indicated that she was ginning weight. She was also found to have a _2__ level. She decided it was best she registered with a GYM close to her house for ___3_ classes. She also needed to have a change of __4____ because she was becoming __5___ to sweet drinks. It was not going to be easy but she made up her mind to give it all it takes to be healthy. (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 3.)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Dance",
      "B": "Reading",
      "C": "Swimming",
      "D": "Walking"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "A student does not need to engage in one of these activities while watching his/her teacher display a diagram in class.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Watching out for major transitional words",
      "B": "Listening",
      "C": "Observing the diagram",
      "D": "Writing major points"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of these activities is best done during study time?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Note making",
      "B": "Note planning",
      "C": "Note taking",
      "D": "Note assessment"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Edward Fry posited that a reader could achieve ___ level of comprehension while reading 800 words per minute.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": 1,
      "B": 0.2,
      "C": 0.6,
      "D": 0.5
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage and fill in the appropriate word in the gap: Everyone truly needs to be careful in these days of increasing _1___ crimes. I got a mail the other day, asking me to __2__ my banking app. The sender promised I would be able to have access to my 3___interests once the process was completed. On a second thought, I decided to speak with my sister who is a banker first. She told me if I had carried out the action, I would have made the criminal a _4___ who would have access to all my lifetime ___5__.  (Choose from the options below, the word that best fits into number 5.)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Sweat",
      "B": "Property",
      "C": "Interests",
      "D": "Earnings"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following aspects of a lecture can a student further develop when writing an assignment?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Topics",
      "B": "Abbreviation",
      "C": "Transitional words",
      "D": "Main points"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the alternative that best gives the meaning of the capitalised word in the sentence: The state has been RESTIVE for about two months now.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Tense",
      "B": "Retrogressive",
      "C": "Peaceful",
      "D": "Progressive"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "A tourist travelling from Nigeria to Columbia will need to acquire information in form of ____",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Narration",
      "B": "Mythology",
      "C": "Fables",
      "D": "Direction"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: Amina is an interesting Nigerian woman. She made up her mind while growing up not to be _1__ by the challenges of her ___2__ environment. She was determined to be __3__ in her career despite being a woman. Years later, her __4_ has paid off, and today she is the CEO of a multimillion dollar company. (Which of the following is the best option for number 3?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Attractive",
      "B": "Outstanding",
      "C": "Outlandish",
      "D": "Opaque"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: Okonkwo and Ige are childhood friends. The duo also attended the University of Lagos. Someone has described them as twins from different mothers and I agree. Which reading strategy did the writer use to make the meaning of words clearer in the passage?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Lexical familiarisation",
      "B": "Co-text",
      "C": "Word attack",
      "D": "Past experiences"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the following options is NOT required for a listener to comprehend a speech",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Global exposure",
      "B": "Familiarity with the vocabulary",
      "C": "General knowledge of the subject",
      "D": "Attention"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the passage: While I was growing up, I lived with my aunty at Ilu Awe. It is a sub urban area in the South Western part of Nigeria. In those days, the people of Ilu Awe were easy going and communal in nature. They were mainly farmers and traders. Some of them were also civil servants. Life was generally peaceful. It was hardly ever the case that one would hear of robbery in that community at that time. I will love to visit the town again.  (Which of the options is the term for this type of text?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Argumentative",
      "B": "Descriptive",
      "C": "Expository",
      "D": "narrative"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following options could be regarded as the highest level of listening activity?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Anticipation of the speaker\u2019s next move",
      "B": "Evaluating speaker\u2019s point of view",
      "C": "Sifting of noise from actual information",
      "D": "Developing a rich vocabulary"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your comprehension rate in a study type reading should be about ______",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "80-90%"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is recommended that in a slow study type reading you should read at least _______ words per minute.",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "200-300"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: Amina is an interesting Nigerian woman. She made up her mind while growing up not to be _1__ by the challenges of her ___2__ environment. She was determined to be __3__ in her career despite being a woman. Years later, her __4_ has paid off, and today she is the CEO of a multimillion dollar company. (Which of the following is the best option for number 1?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Adjudged",
      "B": "Affirmed",
      "C": "Deterred",
      "D": "Propelled"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following conversation:  Teacher: People usually refer to this object as\u2026..? Pupil: Telephone Teacher: Telephone, Yes, yes, you are correct. (Which of the following listening enabling skills did the pupil employ in the exchange?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Comprehension",
      "B": "Functioning ears",
      "C": "Anticipation",
      "D": "Relationship"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of these terms refers to the most exciting point in a story",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Plot",
      "B": "Argument",
      "C": "Climax",
      "D": "Exposition"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following options may likely influence how a listener distinguishes between facts and fables?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "World view",
      "B": "Attention",
      "C": "Functioning ears",
      "D": "Vocabulary"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "The study speed is also known as the ___ speed.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Average",
      "B": "Slowest",
      "C": "Fast",
      "D": "Fastest"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: As a Nigerian, Olubiyi is __1__ with regards to language use. His father had many wives and the polygamous nature of his family exposed him to diverse cultures. His friends accuse him of being ___2__ because he can hardly keep secret. His wife however believes he is not as unserious as everyone thinks but that he could actually be _3__ when assessing situations. (Which of the following is the best option for number 3?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Fidgety",
      "B": "Negative",
      "C": "Critical",
      "D": "Complex"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage: Amina is an interesting Nigerian woman. She made up her mind while growing up not to be _1__ by the challenges of her ___2__ environment. She was determined to be __3__ in her career despite being a woman. Years later, her __4_ has paid off, and today she is the CEO of a multimillion dollar company. (Which of the following is the best option for number 4?)",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Indolence",
      "B": "Malevolence",
      "C": "Resilience",
      "D": "Competence"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following will likely happen when a participant at an inaugural lecture writes without adequate understanding of what the lecturer is saying?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "s/he will include extraneous information",
      "B": "s/he will include fallacious expressions in the content",
      "C": "s/he will use wrong vocabulary in writing",
      "D": "s/he will misrepresent the speaker"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following conversation: Speaker A: Mr Tolu! Mr Tolu! (calling out to a man standing not too far from him)  Speaker B: Don\u2019t bother. When last did you see Mr Tolu? Speaker A: Last year. Speaker B: That\u2019s a long time. He reacted to an antibiotic some time ago and it affected him seriously. You can see he is reading a newspaper. He doesn\u2019t know you are calling him.  Speaker A: Ah! How do I communicate with him then?  Speaker B: Write the information on a piece of paper and go and give him.    Which of the options appropriately describes Mr Tolu\u2019s challenge as a listener?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Relationship",
      "B": "Anticipation",
      "C": "Concentration",
      "D": "Functioning ears"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "A student from one of these disciplines may not require copious use of symbols when writing during a lecture.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Biochemistry",
      "B": "Information Technology",
      "C": "Actuarial science",
      "D": "Classics"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following options may help a reader determine which aspect of a book to read?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Introduction",
      "B": "Appendix",
      "C": "Index",
      "D": "Summary"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following passage:  As a Nigerian, Olubiyi is __1__ with regards to language use. His father had many wives and the polygamous nature of his family exposed him to diverse cultures. His friends accuse him of being ___2__ because he can hardly keep secret. His wife however believes he is not as unserious as everyone thinks but that he could actually be _3__ when assessing situations.  Which of the following is the best option for number 3?",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "Fidgety",
      "B": "Critical",
      "C": "Negative",
      "D": "Complex"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the option that gives the meaning of the capitalized word: The pastor of the blue roofed church is quite CHARISMATIC.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "charming ",
      "B": "repugnant",
      "C": " boorish ",
      "D": "apathetic"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the option that gives the meaning of the capitalized word: Capable lawyers with business ACUMEN are valuable to any firm.",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": " insensitivity\n",
      "B": "ingenuity\n ",
      "C": "ineptness\n ",
      "D": "obtuseness"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reading at the fastest speed is needed when you want to _______",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "locate information quickly"
  },
  {
    "question": "One important way of increasing your vocabulary is to _______",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "read intensively and extensively"
  },
  {
    "question": "The_______ needs high concentration and particular attention to specific details.",
    "type": "fill",
    "options": {
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    "answer": "study reading speed"
  },
  {
    "question": "For a poor reader to achieve a comprehensive rate of 80 \u2013 90%, the study speed may be as low as _______",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "120 \u2013 180 words/min ",
      "B": "60 \u2013 100 words/sec",
      "C": " 60 \u2013 125 words/min",
      "D": " 30 - 45 words/min"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": " In English lexicon, words that cut across all fields are called ________",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "lexical compounds ",
      "B": "specified diction",
      "C": " field registers",
      "D": " common-core words"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "A listening activity where you listen and link all details to the topic and form your own overall impression is known as _______",
    "type": "mcq",
    "options": {
      "A": "listening for critical evaluation ",
      "B": "listening for general impression ",
      "C": "listening for a specific impression ",
      "D": "listening for the overlapping details in the speech of the speaker"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  }
];
